# Kyle Owen Ga

gakyleowen@gmail.com (+63) 939-119-2839 DECA HOMES Cabantian Davao City, Davao Region

### Summary

An ambitious software engineer with three years of experience in Javascript, C#, React.js, Vue.js, Express.js, .Net, MongoDB, Postgresql, MVC, Graphql API, and REST API. Constant learner and ability to adapt to new technologies. Possess strong communication and team management skills.

#### Education

## Information Technology

AMA Computer College • Davao City, Davao Region 2019–2022 **Dean's Lister** 

08/2022

#### Skills

JavaScript, C#, React.js, Next.js, Express.js, Vue.js, .Net, Shopify, Hubspot,

MongoDB, Postgre, Mysql, Git, GitHub

#### Experience

## Developer II

FWD Springboard Student Challenge • Davao City, Davao Region

09/2021 - 11/2021

- Won **Top 3** in the National Level
- · Developed a social media mobile application (with React Native) that allows easy access to insurance globally

Developer II 02/2022 - 05/2022

Web-based Fire Safety Inspection Certification System of Bureau of Fire Protection (Davao City) • Davao City, Davao Region

· Built the front-end for the Certification System for Applicants and Bureau of Fire Protection Employees

## **Developer Lead**

Hill&Foster Web Design and Branding agency

• Implementing and creating impactful designs as the lead frontend developer

05/2022 -11/2024